▶ Dao Long Thinh

Internship / Fresher Front-end Developer

Phone: 0869 041 103

Địa chỉ: 32/80, Phan Sao Nam, Tan Binh, Tp.HCM

E-mail: thinhdao202@gmail.com

Github: github.com/LongThinh20

Facebook: facebook.com/thinhdao202



Summary

Hi! My name is Dao Long Thinh, my brithday is 20/02/1994, after a period of research I decided to learn about frontend after 2 years of military service.

Although I still have many difficulties about knowledge, but with my high determination, I will try to develop myself more to have good job opportunities and hope to contribute to the development of the company.

Education

10/2012 – 7/2015 Mechatronics – Caothang Technical College, Ho Chi Minh City.

• Grade: Average (6.9 / 10)

2/2020 - 11/2020 Cybersoft Academy - Frontend Master

• **Programming Course:** Java Basic, Frontend Master.

 Front-end Foundation course: basic knowledge HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, SASS/SCSS, Javascript(ES6), Git,...

• **Grade:** Verry good (8.5 / 10).

11/2021 - present Cybersoft Academy - NodeJs

- Programming Course: NodeJs.
- Back-end Foundation course: ES6, Nodejs ExpressJs, SocketIO...

Experience

7/2016 – 8/2016 Technician at FPT Telecom

Technical support via call center, receiving requests for technical troubleshooting, booking troubleshooting appointments.

3/2017 - 11/2019 Join the army

 Practice self-discipline, military style to work quickly on time,...

2/2020 - 11/2020 Study at Cybersoft Academy

- Be provided with knowledge from basic to advanced, coding with projects from simple to complex during the time I studied.
- With each part of the knowledge learned, I have been given extra homework and classwork.

Skills

HTML/CSS HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, SCSS, Responsive

Javascript ES6, AXIOS

ReactJS Basic , Redux , React Hooks

GIT Git Basic

Soft skills Teamwork, self study

Project

MY PORTFOLIO

(4/2021 - present)

Link	 Link demo: myportfolio-main.netlify.app/ Link Github: LongThinh20/My_Portfolio.git
Description	My portfolio where you can get information online and visit my done project.
Team size	1
Position	Developer
Responsibility	 Development, optimize code and fix bugs.
Technology	HTML5, CSS3, SASS/SCSS, ES6, Wowjs, Swiper.

ONE PAGE

Link	 Link demo: portfolio-sass.herokuapp.com/ Link Github: github.com/LongThinh20/OnePage_Portfolio.git
Description	A clone UI website ONE PAGE with responsive.
Team size	1
Position	Developer
Responsibility	Development, optimize code and fix bugs.
Technology	HTML5, CSS3, SASS/SCSS, ES6, Wowjs, owl-carousel.

BOOKING_TICKET

Link	 Link demo: bookingticket-reactjs.netlify.app/ Link Github: github.com/LongThinh20/Project Booking Ticket.git
Description	A clone UI website galaxy cinema, booking ticket, login, logout and display user information with responsive.
Team size	1
Position	Developer
Responsibility	 Development, optimize and fix bugs.
Technology	 HTML5, CSS3, Boostrap 4, SASS/SCSS, ReactJs, Redux, Axios, Hooks